Narrator: 3A
M: Oh no!
Where’s my phone?
Where are my glasses?
What is it?
What are they?
It’s an ID card.
They’re keys.
What’s in your bag?
I have two bank cards.
Narrator: 3B
M: How much is this mug?
How much are these key rings?
They’re twenty pounds.
A T-shirt, please.
Is this your phone?
Thank you very much.
You’re welcome.
souvenirs
here
there
Narrator: 4A
M: Come in.
Be good.
Let’s order pizza.
on the table
in my phone
Mum
Dad
a babysitter
What a lovely card!
Can I see?
I remember.
Perhaps.
Narrator: 4B
F: sir
madam
an electric car
a sports car
easy to park
perfect
in her opinion
Is the car for you?
I prefer that red car.
I love it!
Come with me.
a museum
a village
a motorbike
famous